Dad. Mom?
Kazuma here!
This world is under constant threat
of the Devil King's generals.
Wait, I guess I already told you about them.
Sorry about that.
Anyway, your son's been getting
a lot of female attention lately.
In fact, one even wants to have my baby,
and ladies with very explosive proportions
have made some pretty spicy advances.
In other words,
you might be meeting your grandchild
sooner than we thought.
Hey! It's Kazuma, the one who took down
another general!
It's Kazuma who's a candidate for being a hero!
Kazuma is incredibly rich!
Please marry me!
Settle down, ladies.
Because there's only one of me to go around.
Aww!
Okay, okay!
Whoa-ho!
Aren't you a feisty one?
Try and relax.
Now, come on.
This is no place for you.
Okay! What's with you?
Uh-uh-uh-uh!
Quit it, will ya?
I happen to be a traditional guy
who appreciates a proper courtship!
I'm touching you on purpose.
Huh?
I like you.
I love you!
And it's all on purpose!
Well, here's my god.
The mele or the Peach
The Mele
Megamine.
Yeah?
What do you want?
Know where our Crimson Demon Village souvenirs are?
Oh, those?
I noticed some empty bottles of bubbly,
so I threw them out.
But that doesn't make sense.
Hey Kazuma!
Hey, Kazuma! You wouldn't happen to know where all my bubbly went, would you?
Huh?
Hey, are you even listening to me? Those were mine, and you can't...
The wind.
Huh?
And the sun.
Are you feeling okay? That seems unusually profound.
Kazuma's finally reached that age. He's been muttering things like that quite a bit lately.
And to be honest, I totally understand it.
What? What's going on? You're freaking out and starting to freak me out, too!
Tell you what, forget about the bubbly, okay?
Forget about the what?
Konosuba!
What brings the four of you in here so early?
Gah!
An awesome reward for saving the whole crimson demon village!
So bring up all of the bubbly of Gat!
Whoa, slow your roll, you useless goddess!
You should make sure you can pay for this before you!
Some more bubbly right over here, please!
Oh, and I'd like to have some tea, miss!
Megumin, you are not old enough yet!
But that isn't fair!
I want to have a drink, too!
You can forget it, so don't even try it!
No drinking for Loli!
Damn!
How about treating me to some of that?
Looks like...
Don't you ever stand behind me!
Oh, yes.
Oh, the wind.
Ko!
No!
Su!
Ba!
I think I should join the faith.
Huh?
What brought this on all of a sudden?
You're going to be one of those monks with a shiny head?
Not a requirement.
Hang on a minute, Kazuma!
If you're looking to serve a church, then I would recommend the Order of Axis!
Oh, hell no.
That's where I draw the line.
Could you at least explain this all to us?
Oh, yes.
Orcs, and PTSD from a lover's suicide with a chimera.
In the end, I was dead wrong!
You're so exhausted.
I'll share some words of wisdom with you.
In the Axis Order, when...
Stop right there!
That kind of advice is what got me in this situation!
Never again, understand?
Never!
I'm changing jobs from adventurer to monk, damn it!
And no one can stop me!
Saying goodbye to your daredevil days?
Uh-huh.
There'll be some times in your life when you feel like doing that.
Especially when you're a young man.
But luckily for you, there is infinite potential.
Thanks, man.
I need some directions to the nearest temple.
All right, what discipline exactly?
I think we better make it an extremely strict one.
Uh, okay.
Well, I do have this.
It's quite a journey, but...
Oh, yes!
Thank you so much!
For everything!
Oh, by the way!
I had a huge crush on you!
Oh, no!
Kazuma!
Wait a minute!
You want to try and reconsider this, Kazuma?
Absolutely.
Maybe after a good night's sleep.
Trust me!
Everything's gonna be all right!
We'll start getting desperate for a little bubbly by the time the sun sets!
Ugh!
Shut up!
I'm not like you, you useless goddess!
Oh!
So you're calling me that again, huh?
Well, if the useless shit fits...
Goodbye.
EXPLOSION!
You're kidding.
I've got to resolve as firm as that mountain over there!
That's real convincing!
Coming from someone with the mental resilience of tofu like Kazuma!
That's enough!
Now grit those teeth!
Cause I've got a gender equality punch with your name on it!
Now settle down, Kazuma!
And stop laughing, Aqua!
It's nothing but immature nonsense.
In times like these, call me assessing ones.
Pretty hilarious coming from the loli archetype!
Tell me, is that flimsy little frame of yours ever gonna hit a growth spurt?
That's it.
I had to think I was trying to show some restraint.
Very well, then.
Now I am going to blow your resolve to smithereens!
It was that mountain right!
No!
EXPLOSION!
It's been a while since we slept under the stars like this.
Don't get sentimental with me and think you can get out of it.
No one's carrying you tomorrow.
We should've already been there by now.
I'm doing it on...
I can't!
What?
Ah!
Huh?
Ah?
Ah!
Huh?
and foresight but don't worry back home all-nighters were a regular thing for
me you're used to staying up all night what led to a life like that well my uh
my friends and I would raid enemy fortresses tackling dangerous bosses
usually on no sleep at all that's extraordinary and there's not an air of
falsehood whatsoever he's exuding genuine confidence and even a slight tinge of
nostalgia yeah right those were all video games if anything happens just wake me
up even if you have to be wrong cool I'll do it all animal style if you need
reminding there are certain lines you should never cross his comrades it's
funny how that works when you tell the real man not to cross the line that's
when the urge is strongest you're trying to make that sound like a good thing are
you
so um have you ever considered leaving here and going back home even if I wanted to I can never do
that what would your parents think if they knew you wanted to join the faith oh pipe down all right
because I've already decided you helped me I maintained my connection to explosion
magic thanks to you
up to this point you've only seen an explosion that would earn a score of 120
points someday I want to show you one that's a perfect 200
I mean living with you guys hasn't been all bad or anything I the reward for saving the crimson demon
village is coming to good point and it's not like becoming a monk will suddenly bring me peace
wait my deal with veneer wasn't finished either considering all the money that's coming in maybe
it'd be nice to just relax with the rest of you for a while I like my life as it is too so I hope
nothing changes and when there's danger I know we're gonna get through it because we can overcome any
obstacle together
wait what the hell so great about having to overcome danger
oh
hazma
I wish I wish things could stay the way they are for all of us
holy crap this is so damn bittersweet
what's she doing what's with the hand maybe I really did hit a popular phase
should I make a move right now maybe you ought to say something really smooth
hey who the hell do you think I am I'm way too pure for that calm down take a deep breath first
okay
Megamine I maybe I won't join
it's just past these woods a new chapter in my life is beginning
you'll come crying back home in no time so I'll be waiting for you with some chill bubbly boo
shut it aqua hey Megamine what happened back there what exactly did he do to you
who could that be
she's hurt pretty badly hey are you
hang on that's a monster in disguise
my enemy detection's going crazy right now
oh
hey
i'm getting the strange urge to go over to that girl and cast heel on her
tranquility girl's a species of plant monster this dangerous breed of creature is known to evoke
an intense protective instinct in passing travelers
hey kazuma this girl looks like she's about to burst into tears any minute
when in her presence she will begin exhibiting a reassuring smile that makes it difficult to pass
her by the more good nature to traveler is the greater the threat this monster poses caution is advised
that's a monster the guilds put out a hit on
i'm gonna heal your wounds okay you'll be good as new in no time
oh
how weird these look like bandages but that's not what they seem to be at all
what's going on here your reaction is how she catches travelers
and then after they starve she starts digging her roots in
whoa what do you think you're doing kazuma don't you come any closer oh come on it's not like i
i want to but we don't have any choice here you're killing me she can talk
really you're giving me that look now you can relax because i can get him to shut up with these holy
fists of mine
you're killing me
try and get a grip on yourself damn it that thing's a killer
would it be worse to let her go and move on we're trying to deal with her myself right here and now
kazuma
any decision you make that you're not quite sure of
is one you'll always have second thoughts about so just choose whichever is easiest in the moment
what kind of advice is that does she think i'm some sort of idiot
please forgive me i'm so sorry this is all because i'm alive is that right
i'm nothing more than a monster so my very existence makes others uncomfortable for the first time
in my whole life i've been given the honor of actually speaking to humans
i'm so glad you good people were the first and the last i'll ever meet if one day
i'm reborn into this world i hope i don't come back here as a monster please no
how the hell am i supposed to kill her now
man this sucks a monster you feel bad about whether you take it down or not you surprised me
kazuma guess you still do have a heart i'm a good guy well she did tell us that we were the first
human she's ever even spoken to so i doubt she's claimed any victims yet oh wait a sec is something
wrong does your tummy have the grumbles i've got some extra paper you can use would you quit it
it just hit me there's something i gotta do i'll be back in a minute
how poopy is dance would you drop it
this mountain path leads to the temple i have to go back out there and ask her not to hurt anyone
who might show up oh yeah and if i'm able to tuck some sense into her then i'll offer to bring her
food from the temple every day this is such a great idea who knows maybe me becoming a monk
what's fate i bet it was it must have been
hey
those dorks looked really nice and meaty too i bet they would have made an amazing meal
damn i wonder where i went so wrong
you're killing me
i just hope
i just hope that if i'm reborn
maybe humans or family or good friends oh i should use good friends yes that's the one it'll get him for sure
if i'm lucky enough to be reborn i just hope that we can all be good friends
oh yeah this is so gonna work
this loser is basically all dried up now i'll have to take down the next sucker who shows up with my brand new lines
okay time to photosynthesize well they're so nice
oh
we good friends can you pretend not hear anything
you can talk perfectly this entire time you dumbass
you're my friend you're my good friend
let's go home
i see things a lot clearer now so let's head back to axel
are you sure kazuma
yup
you're looking all refreshed
must have been a big one
yup
i bet it was rough with no paper
i told you it wasn't that
huh
hey what's up with the mallet
oh i came across a body i buried and found this so i figured i should grab it
huh for some strange reason i feel like i've seen it before
let me take a closer look at that seriously you need to be careful it's not a toy this might
actually be worth something to let go of it already
no
huh
i'm doing it on purpose
on purpose i'm doing this on purpose
damn it i'm smashing into you
kazuma kazuma
there's some fancy bubbly around here that i've been waiting to get my hands on
well we're gonna buy it then it's amazing how financial security can make a big difference
on your whole state of mind hey
chris wow seems like you're even cheerier than usual
we're about to celebrate kazuma's return his return
do you want to join us don't you worry because money is no object
it sounds nice but i've still got some stuff to do next time okay yeah definitely bye
kazuma kazuma i have had my eye on this beautiful robe oh yeah we can get that too
i'll just shake our magic mallet and
hmm
i'm never leaving again a shut-in like me never should have gotten such big ideas
it's too bad we don't have the mallet but i'm glad to have you here and back to normal
yeah well he's definitely back to being a full-time loser if that's what you mean
but the weird thing is it's sort of comforting makes me realize that actually trying is sort of
overrated anyway don't let that sloth affect you too uh excuse me huh is there anybody at home
hello hello
is anybody
oh what's going on here stop knock it off i don't know who you are or what this is but i bet it's
trouble so leave us alone you jigs
kazuma your strange touchstone is knocked down and face out on the floor you can toss this guy out
and say no one ever can stop it
bye
kono zuma
haugen what brings you way out here at this time of night my lady i have bad news i'm afraid your only
assets may be in grave danger wait she's not gonna shriek is she this naughty body of hers is just
gonna dry up what in the world are you saying no not that the family is on the verge of losing
it standing which would then leave the young mistress without her only real asset her privilege
that may be even more insulting wait this is it's the seal of the royal family
what is it saying no nothing whatsoever you've no need to be concerned i assure you
give me that no please you said it once before remember you don't want any trouble
which is the reason that i steal please i beg you let it go greetings sarcasima sato who has slain
quite an impressive number of the devil king army's generals it would give me great pleasure to hear
of your heroic exploits in person and i'm extending dinner invitations to that end signed iris first
princess
kazuma you cannot go you haven't any manners if this goes wrong you could be beheaded
i have an idea if good food is what you want i'm sure we could rent out a nice restaurant this is
officially the dawning of a new age
kill me
and this right here and now strike me down
yes we are still going
going up
まだ満ちなかった
その僕らの夢に
終わらない賛美を
胸の奥で
なり続ける夜も
耳を塞りたくなるような時もあるね
まだだまだまだだ
主役は遅れて現れる
いつものパターンもそっと愛想
道ながばだっていいじゃないか
怖くないわけじゃない
ただ強いだけじゃない
それでも聞こえる
自由のうたを
歌ってハート
Go on
夢中なままでいいんだよ
世界は派手さ
手探りの勇気が掴む
未来はきっと
Shining now
何回も
僕ら重ねたこの日に
かけがえのない
虹が掛かると
大使は言ってて
石を入れて
共に彼方へ
終わりない旅路に
素晴らしい袋に
祝福を
飛沢